Guide to the James N. Wells' Sons Records 1700s-1981 (bulk, 1820s-1930s) MS 599
New-York Historical Society
- 3 rolled objects. Restricted due to fragility, 1872, undated (Offsite-box 39)
  Map: "Moore, Franklin & Robinson, DeKay, Eckford and Clarke Estates." Map: "Map of the Common Lands From 26th Street to 43rd Street, showing the Old Streets and Plots as Surveyed and Mapped in 1796 by Cassimer T.H. Goerek, City Surveyor, and the Distance between those Old Streets and our Present Streets" by J.B. Holmes, City Surveyor, July 1872 Rolled item: labeled on outside as "North River View." Not unrolled due to fragmenting.
- Unidentified fragments of blueprint(s), 1930, undated (Offsite-box 39)
  Restricted. The fragments require conservation humidification, flattening, and piecing together before use. It is not clear if the fragments are from one or multiple blueprints. One fragment indicates it is from 1930. Another indicates it is from a first floor plan, and various fragments indicate that the plan includes space for several stores.